Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
The hostility which is getting worse
between two Beys...
needs to end.
The solution is clear.
It is to marry their daughter.
What I want from you is to marry
Malhun Hatun.
My Sheik...
I am already married.
It's your daughter.
She can't give birth.
You have to have a son in order for
Kayı Tribe to have a future.
You can't postpone it any further.
Do you see how they're looking at you?
They trust you, they believe in you.
You are responsible for them, Osman Bey.
You have to show your heir to them by...
marrying a Bey's daughter who will
enrich your tribe.
I know, my Sheik.
I know.
But how can I do this to Bala?
Bala knows what's going to happen.
But...
Malhun Hatun would hurt her, my Sheik.
Think about it.
Let me know when you decide.
I have no doubt that you'll
decide on the best.
Let's go Kumral Abdal.
We are done here.
Off we go, my Sheik.
Alps.
We are returning to the tent.
- Umur Bey is absent.
- What do you mean?
He is absent, Nicola!
There is nothing but crows where
he and his Alps should be.
Sir, Togay is coming with his soldiers.
- What are we going to do Nicola?
- Shut up.
They don't know we're here.
We can have a sudden arrow attack.
I told you to shut up! We lost
Bitinya because of fools like you!
We can't defeat Togay with a bunch of
soldiers we have!
Sir, they are coming!
What are we going to do Nicola?
Go back to your castle.
Pay your tax.
- I can't do it.
- I told you to do it.
You'll do it!
Let Togay think he dominates us.
Patience.
A little bit more patience.
Damn patience.
Go back to your castle.
We're returning to castle!
We are returning to castle!
The hostility which is getting worse
between two Beys needs to end.
The solution is clear.
It is to marry their daughter.
He hampers my trade!
He stops me from fighting against
my biggest enemy!
Osman Bey crossed the line!
How much longer is he going to
fade out my tribe's future?
If he didn't stop me...
He shouldn't have stopped me!
If Edebalı hadn't stopped me...
I missed the opportunity to take revenge,
to cut that dog's throat!
Do you see what Osman Bey who you
support all the time does?
Do you see how he stops my rise in the
eyes of other Turkmen Beys?
Are we going to trust this man
about future?
My Bey, Osman Bey's intention was not
to stop your rise.
Then what?
He wanted to make himself clear.
He told us everything.
He made an agreement with Seljuq...
Enough!
I'll go back to my tent if you allow.
I shall come back when you are
ready to hear the truth.
Malhun!
I take back every Alp I gave in
your order!
You'll have no say in any of my business
from now on.
I'll manage Alps.
You'll sit in your tent just like
other tribes' Hatuns.
Now you can go!
Spring is coming my Sheik.
My Lord is scattering his ornaments
to the ground.
Insha Allah the hostility between
Umur Bey and Osman Bey ends...
and spring visits Turkmen tribes too,
my Sheik.
Does spring come without
trees getting rid of their secrets?
Does flowers bloom, Kumral Abdal?
My Osman Bey has to do the difficult.
He needs to get rid of his secret and
let the flower in his heart bloom.
Obviously, he is afraid of hurting
his flower, my Sheik.
Spring doesn't come if
you don't get cold, Kumral Abdal.
Both my beloved Bala and
Osman Bey...
are going through hard times.
They are going to be patient.
They are going to be hurt.
Then they're going to heal.
This is the only way.
As I have no one else other
than you in my heart...
I have no intention to look for
someone else other than you, Bala.
You are my prayer.
You shall be with me.
Having children is Allah's decision.
How can a little dagger wound
seperate us...
while we are in so much
love with each other, my Bala?
Bala.
Sit.
Since when have you been here, my Bey?
I was watching you.
What were you thinking about?
My Sheik father...
didn't let me go to you at once.
He said no first.
I was daydreaming, watching
the candles...
in the Dergah(where Dervishes live).
I couldn't tell if the fire is in
the candle or in my heart.
So...
what do you feel now?
You are my candle now.
And I am a fan in your fire.
Finally...
you bow to me, Nicola.
What about Osman Bey's tax?
Osman Bey will pay to Sultan.
He thinks he can hide his taxes
in Turkmen Beys' eyes.
This doesn't matter after obeying
persians.
You sweared
on Cenghiz Khan's life to kill Osman...
I am afraid that you make the
souls angry, Togay!
My swear will not end until this land...
becomes grave to...
one of us, and until one of us
is sacrificed to the souls, Camu!
Only blood can save us from the
wrath of souls!
Osman will send messenger.
He'll announce he obeys us one more time.
Be patient.
Go now.
You'll have no say in any of my business
from now on.
I'll manage Alps.
You'll sit in your tent just like
other tribes' Hatuns.
Will I sit in my tent?
Can I come in?
Come.
What do you say, Alaca Hatun?
What should I do with this sword?
Now that I am not fighting...
I am not going to be honored
by the holiness of war...
Should I melt it in the fire and make
jewellery out of its steel?
Or should I sell it to a junk dealer?
Don't talk like that!
It's the sharpest sword of
Kızılbeyoğulları.
Don't worry.
Your father will change his mind.
How are my Alps doing?
They don't want to retreat.
They want to fight under you.
They want you to know that they
are under your dominance.
Tell them to be ready.
I'll talk to them.
Elhamdulillah. (Thanks to Allah)
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
We haven't had such a feast
for a while.
Boran Alps keeps talking about it.
I can't cook game meat
as well as Bala.
Enjoy your meal.
I learned it from Akca and Dervishes
in Dergah (where dervishes live).
My Osman, you haven't hunted
for some time.
Doesn't infidels count, my Bala?
What did you think of, my Bey?
When I was this little...
We went hunting with my father one day.
But it was my first time
hunting on horse.
Then my father started explaining.
He said, "you'll get up on horse...
you'll grasp the horse with your feet...
then you're going to focus on your prey...
then you'll speed up, speed up...
you'll raise your arrow, stretch
your bow, shoot your prey."
We found the gazalle.
My father went after it.
He did it like he explained.
Then told me that it was my turn.
He also told me that
this skill required experience.
Then we went through forests
and rivers...
We arrived at a huge valley.
We followed the gazelle so far.
Then I focused, prepared my arrow...
stretched my bow, and taaak,
I shot it.
My father was surprised.
He said "you did it."
And I replied "yes father, you showed me,
I shot." That's what I said.
My father told this to my brothers
all the night over and over.
"You showed me, I shot."
Good old days.
He didn't expect you to shot
it in your first time, my Bey.
To be honest, I haven't heard something
like that too. Masha Allah (praise be).
Ertugrul Ghazi was proud so much of you,
my Bey.
Of course he did, my Gonca. My Bey will be
proud of his children when he has.
Eeh, my Bey. You must have missed hunting,
we can do it, huh?
Yes, yes we shall go hunting.
We'll go right away.
We'll go tomorrow.
I'll take sherbet.
I'll help you Bala.
My Bey, forgive me.
I couldn't figure my words.
My Bala...
I apologize for Boran Alp.
He had no bad intention.
There's nothing to apologize for, my
Gonca. Boran Alp said nothing wrong.
Every father is proud of their children.
And my Osman Bey can't be a father...
I paid my tax to Togay.
What did he say?
He thinks he is the only governor
in Bitinya.
Only Bitinya?
That dog thinks he is the only
governor in the whole world!
He said Osman obeyed Mongols
after Konya visit.
Is that so?
Osman must have convinced Sultan.
What Sultan wants is to
protect his position.
Geyhatu is like a bankrupting merchant.
They both need gold to save their
positions. They don't care about Osman.
The only thing they want is gold.
Are we going to pay tax until
we go dry?
For how long will this go on, Nicola?
If Togay and Osman are in peace...
we have to destroy that peace.
We should set them against
each other, right, Yason?
How will you do that?
Umur Bey.
We'll wait for the coward who even
couldn't...
come to the trap we set for him.
Is that right?
Osman must have stopped him.
But this won't turn off the hatred
in Umur Bey against Togay.
Umur will come to me sooner or later.
How will you set Osman and Togay
against each other?
Whether he accepts or not,
Umur is under Osman's umbrealla
For how long do you think a honorable and
stubborn Bey like him can put up with Osman?
Here another question, Yason.
In a scenario in which Umur attacks Togay,
what happens?
As Umur is under Osman's patronage...
Osman would be responsible
for this attack.
Well done.
So...
Whom will Togay hit at?
- At Osman.
Peace coming from gold
melts by blood.
Even Mongol's puppet Sultan Mesut
can't save Osman now.
Bring me wine!
I'll be patient and wait now.
I'll wait for Umur to come to me.
You go back to your castle.
Wait for my order.
My Bey will be proud of his children
when he has.
My Bey.
Why are you upset?
It's all because of me that
you don't have a child.
If you don't have a heir, it's because
your Hatun can't give birth.
I saw how your eyes were smiling while
talking about your father Ertugrul Ghazi.
Being a father,
having a heir is your right.
Even it is your duty.
My father's bequest is in my memory.
I remember it.
You...
You shall not hurt yourself...
by thinking these, my Bala.
Don't think about it.
Everything will be what they'll be.
I know you're going to decide on the best.
You're thinking about a Hatun that
would hurt Bala least.
This is why your decision is late.
I know it.
But I am okay with this.
I am okay with my fate.
You should know that.
We agreed on a decision with Sultan
about Togay issue in Konya.
Now it's time to send a messenger to
Togay.
I appoint Goktug for this mission.
I am at your service my Bey.
My Bey, we prepared accommodation
for refrugees as you ordered.
Eyvallah, but that issue is not done yet.
Help them settle.
Take care of their needs.
Yes my Bey.
My Beys, I have to consult you...
about an important subject.
Tell us Osman Bey.
We are listening.
This may seem a personal subject,
but it actually interests Kayı's future.
You know about our continual
problems with Umur Bey.
Sheik Edebalı think that I have to
marry Malhun Hatun...
in order these problems to end.
This will be a political marriage.
I wanted to hear your opinions.
Eyvallah, Eyvallah Osman Bey.
If this marriage will make Umur Bey
stand with us...
it surely is good.
Malhun Hatun is proper for you, and
she is noble.
But, Osman Bey, this is
easy to tell for us...
but it's hard to do it for you.
Malhun Hatun has been on your side
all the time, Osman Bey.
She supported you
when we had aid from Inegol...
and she even fought on your side
in the war.
Now that you need a heir...
That heir's mother should be noble and
valiant...
as his father.
And this is Fard.
This will be between us for now.
Of course it will be.
Osman Bey, what I see is that
you know what's going to happen.
But I also see that you are worried
about Bala Hatun.
Osman Bey, postponing it won't help
you.
You shall tell her as soon as possible.
I'll have decided when I return from
hunting, Bamsı Bey.
Eyvallah, I wish the best for us.
Amen.
As Alaca Hatun said...
There are alps who would disobey
Umur Bey for me.
And they are a lot in number.
- Is that true, Rasid?
- Yes it is.
We have been at your service
for as long as we can remember.
At my service, under Umur Bey's flag.
Tell me, who are with me?
I want to see.
You supported us in every mistake we made.
You healed some of us...
you helped some of us to marry.
We are with you.
You remember the goodness, yes.
We are the steel swords waiting for you
to command us, Malhun Hatun.
Steel swords waiting for me to command
you, huh?
What can I do with a stupid sword, huh?
What shall I do with a sword that
raises against his Bey?
Malhun Hatun.
Alps!
Look around Alps!
You are in Umur Bey's land!
Pull yourselves together!
This tent's Bey is Umur Bey.
No one can disobey him!
You shall sink that in!
If anyone is to disobey Umur Bey...
He'll face my sword first!
Dark Osman.
What, Kumral Abdal?
What are you looking at?
Is there anyone other than me
who calls you Dark Osman?
Yes, there isn't.
Tell me.
Why are you calling me that?
I heard you are going hunting.
Yes.
- The mountains missed me.
- Yes.
Me either. I missed the sound of the
forests and shadows of the mountains.
Tell me I can come too.
Come on, say that.
Come on.
Okay, then.
You can come with us too.
Don't let these mountains be alone.
Yes!
You!
A disgrace!
Traitor!
Stop!
Cerkutay.
Look at you.
You betrayed the rules of Genghis Khan.
Turks enslaved you.
Cerkutay obeys Allah's rules.
Camuka.
We are here as Osman Bey's messengers.
Search him.
We are not traitors like
your messenger, Camuka
Shut up.
Follow me.
Brothers.
You will stay here.
Seljuqs will pay Osman Bey's golds
with the order of Seljuqs Sultan.
Osman.
He finally found the right way.
We don't care from where it is coming...
if we will get gold.
Whether it is from Osman Bey or...
from Sultan.
We will get your golds until
we get run off your feet.
Every breath you take is tied to the
golds you will give.
As Osman Bey is tied to Geyhatu and me.
Osman Bey wants you to know
that we stick to our deal.
Tell Osman Bey...
if he wants to live in these lands...
he will be tied to us.
My anger and the shadow of my sword
will be his death warrant.
He shouldn't forget that.
Now go and tell Osman Bey that...
Dark Shaman Togay sticks
to the deal as well.
Go.
Come on.
He should wait for the day...
I kill his wife and his tent.
Come on.
Our hunt won't be able to smell us.
Stop, my Bey!
Stop!
What did you do, Kumral Abdal?
It was wounded and desperate.
Desperate?
- It was in pain.
- Kumral Abdal...
You wanted to hunt and now
you are wasting our time.
I am sorry, my Bey.
I am sorry.
I don't want to cause...
those gazelles' extinction.
Are they hunted so much?
It's nearly impossible to track them.
Their ears and their eyes are strong.
They can smell the hunters from
miles away.
Hunting these gazelles...
is only possible when a
good hunter like you does it.
Then why are they becoming extinct?
Female gazelles are sick now, my Bey.
They are infertile.
A child comes from Allah.
A wound can't separate us...
because we love each other so much.
Osman.
Don't.
No.
You will have children.
- I won't do good for you.
- You won't do good for me?
Bala.
I fall apart without you.
Being without you is the biggest
obstacle to my tomorrow.
You are my power.
You are my light.
You...
are my dream, you are my love.
It's my biggest dream to marry you...
and have the consent of my Sheikh.
You are my love, Hatun.
It is fine if Allah won't give us...
children.
They were wandering around as groups.
Now they are very few.
As the forests' beauty comes from them...
our father Suleiman ibn
Qutalmish's descendants...
called them the Sultan of the forest.
They are dying out, my Bey.
It is my bequest, Osman...
My bequest...
These gazelles are the most beautiful
things the forest has ever seen.
They are heroes.
They protect themselves.
They are living like a good memory now.
Let's find ourselves another hunt.
I will find you a new hunt.
These mountains and the hills are my home.
I missed here.
I missed here!
Alps!
Follow him.
He shouldn't be alone.
Malhun Hatun?
Malhun Hatun.
What are you doing here?
Bala.
Help me, my Allah.
Help me.
My heart is a stake, my mind is a hammer.
I am stuck between them.
My Allah.
Help me, my Allah.
I didn't hear you came, my Bey.
Welcome.
How was the hunt?
The hunter and the gazelle...
are an old story.
He doesn't want to attack.
However, he has to.
You will if you have to, Osman Bey.
Look at the gazelle's eyes...
before you do.
I made up my mind.
Come here, my Bala.
Come here.
I will marry someone...
to have an heir for Kayı Tent.
It's a good decision, Osman Bey.
Tell me.
Do you have someone in your mind?
Yes.
However, you are in my heart.
As for who I think of...
it is Sheikh Edebalı's request as well.
So, it is my father's request.
My father.
Who is she? Do I know her?
Kızılbeyoğlu...
Umur Bey's daughter...
Malhun Hatun.
Did my father...
tell you this?
Good.
You made a decision.
May it be good for you.
She is noble.
She is beautiful.
She will be a good wife.
She is good for you.
She will give you children.
The heir issue is over now.
It is a decision to
reconcile the two tents.
If you don't want me to...
if you don't want Malhun Hatun...
I will find someone else.
Osman Bey.
You say it is Sheikh Edebalı's request.
He is my father.
He knows me well.
He knows what this decision...
means to me.
What can I say...
if he told you to marry Malhun Hatun?
You will marry her.
Your decision is right.
Malhun Hatun is a good wife for you.
Ertuğrul Ghazi's bequest...
and Sheikh Edebal's request should
be satisfied.
The Kayı Tent should have an heir.
If you excuse me.
I want to be alone.
I am going to meet Nikola.
We couldn't attack Togay as we promised
we would.
He should know we stick to our deal.
Let me come with you.
Nikola must be very angry.
No, no.
You should stay here.
Watch Malhun Hatun.
She shouldn't know I went to meet Nikola.
- Boran.
- Yes, my Bey.
Did you make up for
the losses of refugees?
Yes, my Bey. They have places to stay...
and everything to trade and sell.
Tell Alps to have more guards.
They should do what is
necessary if Yaso wants to take revenge.
Your command, my Bey.
- Salam Alaikum, my Bey.
- Alaikum Salam, brother.
What do we have from Togay?
He bragged when he heard our loyalty.
Let him comfort himself
with his arrogance.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Akça Dervish, you work like a beaver.
We shouldn't stop, my Bey.
Do you ever stop?
The world doesn't even stop.
Our day is better as we have seen you.
Thank you.
- Is my Sheikh here?
- Yes, my Bey.
- Salam Alaikum, my Sheikh.
- Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
You made your decision.
I made a decision, my Sheikh.
If Umur Bey has consent...
I want to tell him my intentions
about Malhun Hatun.
You did what you had to do, Osman Bey.
I will talk to Umur Bey.
The hardest challenge
starts now, Osman Bey.
Bala will learn to be patient.
You will learn to make both
of the Hatuns happy...
and not to make them upset.
And...
you will also take care of your tent.
Pray for me, my Sheikh.
My prayers are with you.
May Allah help you.
Amin.
If you excuse me.
Alps! Come on.
Akça Dervish.
Yes, my Sheikh.
Let Umur Bey know.
- I will talk to him.
- I will take the road, my Sheikh.
After your daughter's
betrayal, now it's you!
I wonder what is your excuse.
- Osman...
- Umur Bey, you even rose against Geyhatu!
You even lost your children!
You bow down to Osman now.
Ah, Umur Bey.
Nikola.
Know your place!
Osman obviously made you do it.
Umur Bey.
You obeyed Osman...
for a little land.
What did he do?
He tied your hands
against your biggest enemy!
Nikola!
Now that he has khilat...
who can hold him?
What will you do?
You will bow down to...
your new Sultan.
Enough!
Enough, Nikola!
I am not done with Togay yet.
What do you mean?
I won't get permission from neither
Osman nor Sultan and Geyhatu...
to cut my enemy's head off.
I am here to talk about this.
If you are still brave...
I want you to know that I
am ready to attack Togay.
We can talk about this Umur Bey but...
how can I be sure of you
won't betray me again?
I set my mind on it!
I want Togay's head.
With you or without you.
Then...
We should go to Söğüt, Gonca.
Whenever you want, my Bala.
We will ask for a girl in marriage.
We have some things to get.
- Who will we ask for, my Bala?
- Malhun Hatun.
Malhun Hatun?
For who?
For Osman Bey.
Osman Bey?
What are you talking about, my Bala?
You heard me, Gonca.
Why is it her?
Why is it Malhun Hatun?
Doesn't Osman Bey know you don't like her?
It is what my Sheikh wants.
Is it?
My Bala.
- Salam Alaikum, my Sheikh.
- Alaikum Salam
I had an important thing to do
in İnegöl but...
I hurried up here when I heard
my Sheikh wants to talk to me.
What happened?
Is it something important?
It is, Umur Bey.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful)
As I said before...
the hostility between the
two Turkmen Beys...
isn't right.
What has to be done is obvious...
to end the hostility and...
to make the two tents closer.
A marriage.
I think the marriage between Osman Bey and
your daughter Malhun Hatun...
will make it happen.
It is you who will decide, Umur Bey.
I am sure you will make the best decision.
My Sheikh...
all of a sudden...
please...
excuse my confusion, my Sheikh.
Whenever you need us, we are ready.
Thank you.
It's appropriate for Osman Bey
to personally come, my sheik.
-I'll be honored to host you.
-Not at all.
Inshallah, we'll come with Osman Bey.
As you want, my sheik.
Now, if you allow me, my sheik.
Go on, Umur Bey.
Thank you.
If you don't want Malhun Hatun, then
I'll find someone else.
Osman Bey, you say that it's
Sheik Edebali's wish.
He is my father. He knows my heart
the best.
He knows best what this decision
means for me.
If he told you to marry Malhun Hatun...
what can I say?
Bala will grin and bear it.
She'll learn to be patient.
Our bey is worried, brother.
It seems that he has troubles, Boran.
He is like this ever since he was with
Sheik Edebali.
They talked privately when we stopped
Umur Bey.
It's about Umur Bey, it seems.
We'll know tomorrow.
-Come on, brother.
Osman Bey, you know...
two grooms is equal to one treat,
they say.
-How is your hand, Bamsı Bey?
-My hand is fine.
It's better. Mashallah.
Osman Bey, it seems like you made that
difficult decision.
I've talked to my sheik.
If Umur Bey accepts it...
-I will marry Malhun Hatun.
-Good.
It was difficult but it's good.
Umur Bey will understand that this is
the best. It's good.
Inshallah. Inshallah.
Inshallah.
Karayel...
Bala Hatun, look at this.
This is so pretty, Bala Hatun.
We should make one for you too.
-I have the same, hatun.
-I'll bring another, Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun, how is this?
With the name of Allah!
Bala. My pretty Bala.
We can leave if you like.
The women can take care of it.
What are you saying, Gonca Hatun?
It's our bey's wedding.
Haven't I told you that I'll have Osman Bey
married with my own hands if I need to?
-You have.
-Haven't I told you that our happiness...
isn't more important than the future
of the state we are founding.
-You have, Bala. You have.
-Then, don't make me sad.
The gifts will be prepared.
Come on.
Choose the best of the fabrics.
Malik is a name of Allah.
The meaning of this name is that...
we aren't the malik, the owner,
of anything.
But the wordly affairs...
make us forget that.
We think that we are the owners of
the escrows.
With staff on your hand, you wander
around mountains, Kumral Abdal.
Don't you have anything.
I handed over the escrows before
Allah wanted me to.
This is the meaning of the verse that say
''Die before dying.''
Even our lives are escrows.
This is the path of those who can
give up on their lives.
What's more difficult than giving
up on your lives?
My sheik knows.
Tell us, my sheik.
Giving up on your loved one.
With the name of Allah.
Come, my love, my loved one.
My pretty daughter. Come.
O' the one who has to give up
on her loved one.
May Allah give you patience.
My sheik, my heart is in fire.
Those who are cleansed from the
dirt of this world...
are the ones whose hearts are
in fire.
Without that fire, eyes can't
get wet.
If those tears don't trop
from those eyes...
the sins can't get washed.
How many sins do I have, my sheik?
I keep crying but I can't
find a cure.
Come.
Father...
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in.
-Do you have any order, my bey?
-No.
Merchants from the east came but couldn't
find you. The alps told me.
I've talked to the merchants.
To put an end to this animosity...
and make the two tribes have
closer connections...
what must be done is certain.
A marriage.
My bey, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Where did you go today?
I was worried.
If you allow me.
If Umur Bey betrays you this time,
it won't end well. We'll face Togay.
No one will stop me this time.
At the entrance of the Raven Valley,
a forest.
When I went to meet
Togay, we found out...
the placements of all his warriors.
According to the intel I got from
my spies...
The passages, the numbers of his
warriors...
their supplies, the traps they've
set against raid...
we pointed them all out on
this map.
Umur Bey, I will be waiting for you
with my soldiers...
at the passage to the valley, before
the water fall.
From the skirts of the hill
to the valley...
at a moment Togay expects the least...
we'll attack his quarters.
What do you say, Umur Bey?
If you are speaking the truth...
this will be easier than I thought.
How soon can you prepare your
soldiers?
If your soldiers are ready,
so are my alps!
-Let's end this tomorrow.
-This soon?
Like branding a wound, swiftly.
What will we do when Umur
gets in the trap?
Then, my military brilliance
will be at play.
-What kind of an attack is in your mind?
-I will go alone.
I will face Togay all alone.
-What are you saying, sir?
-I will face him and say...
Umur Bey will attack you with
his alps.
If Togay knows that Umur's attack
was known by Osman, what happens?
You will make your enemies kill each
other without losing a soldier.
I'll go meet Togay.
Maybe we can break some ice too.
We are grateful for the good.
We seek your protection against the bad.
We are consent with our fates.
Bless the decision that Osman Bey
made...
for his tribe's future, after his father's
will.
My holy Allah, we are consent with
our fates.
We accept anything that
comes from you.
Helps us to get out of
this dark well..
that we fell into with
my wife.
Make Osman Bey have children...
a lineage that will last forever.
We seek your protection, my Allah.
Don't break our unity, my Allah.
-Amin.
May Allah accept, my bey.
Amin, Bala.
Amin.
Umur Bey sent news.
Tomorrow...
we'll go to him with my sheik.
May the outcome be the best, my bey.
-Amin.
May Allah accept, my bey.
Cerkutay, you don't forget what you
hear. Mashallah.
May Allah accept all our prayers, son.
May Allah accept all our prayers,
Bamsı Bey.
Patience, Allah.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come, my child.
Come, come.
May Allah accept.
May Allah accept all our prayers.
Patience, Allah.
-Cerkutay forgot to bring your food.
-Thank you, my child. Thank you.
So, Cerkutay. You don't leave yourself
hungry but...
you leave Bamsı Bey hungry.
-My bey...
when you said we were going to perform
salaat, I forgot it with the excitement.
Mashallah, did you forget to eat
because of the salaat?
No, I ate. I forgot to bring
Bamsı Bey's.
-I should leave, Bamsı Bey.
-Thank you, daughter. See you.
Thank you. See you.
Son, now, you are a Muslim.
Now, we should find you a nice
girl to marry.
My bey, don't worry.
I found one.
-You did?
-I did, my bey.
-Cerkutay.
-Yes.
You must've found an inappropriate match.
Leave it to the elders.
My bey, my bey, my bey.
If we should leave this to the elders.
My heart is on my right.
Take it out, my bey.
My bey.
Erlik Khan!
Send your dark spirits...
the day of vengeance is coming...
the smell of blood is wrapping the
whole world...
may the soil be fed with blood...
may our swords spread death...
may our fire of vengeance burn all
our enemies...
the power of the spirits...
is with Togay the Dark Shaman!
Silence!
You better not tire your soldiers
like this.
They should have the strength to fight
like men.
Umur will visit you soon like
a nightmare.
Tss, tss, tss, tss!
I told you that Osman would betray you,
but you didn't listen!
You will see the result soon.
Your tongue spills poison.
Umur and his alps are morning training
for you. My concern is Osman.
Do you think he would dare to do this
without asking him?
Praeteritum praeteritum.
The past is in the past.
I'm extending an olive branch.
If my information is wrong...
I'm ready to pay the price.
But what if I'm right?
What do you know?
Speak!
Umur learned your position...
from Osman.
They'll come here from the skirts
of the hill.
-How did you learn?
-I don't have a spy at Osman's tribe now.
But I have some at Umur Bey's tribe.
You can't even imagine.
Geyhatu's hunting dog...
Togay the Dark Shaman. I wish
you good hunt.
Camuha, prepare the warriors.
It's time for blood.
Hurry! Hurry!
It's time for blood!
-Boran, have you helped the refugees?
-We have, my bey.
All their needs from shelter to
food will be provided.
-They look happy, Osman Bey.
-They'll have a home.
They'll work and live.
They have right to be happy.
Who knows how they suffered in
Yasu's hands.
-Salam Alaikum!
-Welcome, my bey.
Come, come, come!
Now it's time. A new life
is beginning for you.
-With Allah's approval, inshallah.
-Thank you, Osman Bey.
-We owe you gratitude for what you did.
-Not at all. Not at all.
-May God protect you, Osman Bey.
-Thank you. You too.
You've seen hostility but shown
friendship.
Despite Dimos' betrayal, despite us
having a traitor among us, you were good.
-May God protect you, Osman Bey.
-Us all. Us all.
We all have a part on the making
of this.
You treated us like a friend, not a bey.
May God protect you, Osman Bey.
May your future be bright.
Thank you. But this isn't a farewell.
Söğüt is our land just like Kayı Tribe.
And you will live under my banner
with peace.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you. Alps, help
them carry their stuffs.
-They should be on their way at once.
-Alright, my bey.
These are the signs of the state you
will found, Osman Bey.
I already see it. All the oppressed
people...
find shelter under your banner.
-Inshallah, brother.
We need to go to Umur Bey's tribe.
No good will come from delaying it.
-Prepare the alps.
-As you order, my bey.
-Osman Bey.
-Tell me, brother.
If you allow it, I want to speak to my
brother, not to my bey.
-Tell me, brother.
-It's hard.
It's hard to make your loved one
sad knowingly.
I know that your heart is full
of affection. But don't forget...
Bala Hatun is our precious.
She is the Head Hatun of our tribe
and the pole of our tent.
This will always stay that way.
Be at ease.
Brother, you did the right thing.
Bala.
We've done the preparations as it
fits our tribe, my bey.
You have my blessing.
May Allah bless you too.
-Do you want to see the gifts.
-Bala...
I want to look at you.
Let the gifts be looked
by the receiver.
I want to see the gift
that Allah gave to me.
She will give you children...
it's great.
You can be on your way when
you want, my bey.
You have the deepest place
in my heart.
Even if they make the strongest
sword of the world...
and pierce my heart, they can never
take you out of there.
Never.
I know, Osman Bey.
You have my blessing.
Then, let's go.
Alps!
Take it.
-Where is, Sheik Edebali.
-Our sheik will join us at Söğüt.
Osman Bey.
Is she well?
May Allah bless her.
She is a brave woman.
-Osman Bey, let's go.
-Let's go.
-My heart is burning, Bala.
-You should go now, dark-eyed-one.
Bala, come on. Come on.
Wait, wait! Leave it to me.
Leave it to me.
Leave it.
Is this chest within your means,
guys?
You will fall under it.
Come on.
Let me help.
The apples are from Karacahisar.
But the cart is from Bilecik.
How do you know?
The smell of Bilecik grape is on
the apples.
Do you keep every smell
in your mind?
Tell me your name, so that I can
keep it in my mind.
I don't easily forget.
Göktuğ Alp, you forgot us.
-I need to go.
-Zoe.
A name that you will forget.
Alps.
Help her too.
-Malhun Hatun.
-Have you seen Bahadır Bey?
He and Umur Bey took the alps
and left the tribe.
-Where did they go?
-I don't know, Alaca.
We will find out.
Nikola was right this time.
We are close to Togay's forest.
Nikola must be close. Let's unmount.
We'll sneak into Togay's place.
For the bloody soil.
It's Osman Bey.
What's that?
My sheik, where is Umur Bey?
Apparently, not in the tribe.
What is this?
With the name of Allah.
Welcome. My sheik, you brought
honor.
Come, let's get to the tribe.
A handicraft.
I thought about their love and
find comfort in my death bed.
If I turn into ash like Aslı,
I will die happy.
You are in my life. I won't let you
leave again, Bala Hatun.
If you say so...
ask my father, Osman Bey.
If you allow it, then...
I will tell my father when
he returns.
Thank you, daughter.
Thank you.
-Where is Umur Bey, Malhun Hatun.
-Not at the tribe, Osman Bey. He left.
-Where did he go?
-I don't know, Osman Bey.
Daughter, Umur Bey knew that
we would come.
He was supposed to wait for us.
My sheik, what are those?
Didn't Umur Bey tell you anything?
He didn't, my sheik.
We are here for good deeds.